Guide to the Development Office, Yale School of Drama, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records concerning Yale salute to Cole Porter at Carnegie Hall, circa 1984-1985; Accession 1993-A-086
  - Follow-Up, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Hyatt/Housing, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Income Activity: Ticket Sales, Grants Income, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Insert Program, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Invitation and Printing Samples, Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letter Drafts, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Marketing, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Money, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Musicians: Rehersal in New Haven, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Newsclips, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Numbers, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - October Kickoff, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Performer Lists, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Phones, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Press Clippings, Features, Items, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Professional Services, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Program, Journal, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Program/Journal (History of Drama at Yale), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Program/Journal (Hist. of Drama at Yale, drafts), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Publicity, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Publicity/Reviews, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Recording, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Regional/National Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Reservations/Invitations, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Richards, Lloyd, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Run-Order: First Draft Script, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Samples of Previous Events, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - The Show, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 47 - 49)
  - Singing Groups, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Souvenir Pin, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Stagebill, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Steering Committee Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Steering Committee List, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Tax Exempt Forms, Tax Deductability, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Theater Authority (Unions, Etc…), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Ticket Payments, Reservations, Requests, Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Yale Ticket Prospects, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Ticket Printing, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Ticket Responses (Old), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Ticket Sales: Blanks, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Ticket Sales: Mrs. Boland's Services, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Underwriters and Honoraries, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Volunteers, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Waldorf-Astoria, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Records of the Development Office, 1985-2002; Accession 2005-A-033
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - LLOYD RICHARDS PARTIES -HOLIDAY PARTIES
    - Invitation (Box 1)
    - New Haven Honors Lloyd Richards, 1991 May 25
      - Invitations (Box 1)
      - Thank you contributions (Box 1)
      - New Haven Honors Lloyd Richards - Invitations List (Box 1)
      - Catering (Box 1)
      - Thank You Attending (Box 1)
      - General Information (Box 1)
      - Replies (Box 1)
    - Benno Schmidt's Reception -, 1991 June 3
      - General Information (Box 1)
      - Invitations (Box 1)
      - Invitations List (Box 1)
      - Invoices (Box 1)
    - Los Angeles Lloyd Farewell, 1990 February 11 (Box 1)
    - Lloyd Benefit Thank You (Box 1)
    - Waldorf-Astoria Benefit (Box 1)
    - Lloyd Event Proposals (Box 1)
    - Commemorative Program Ads (Box 1)
    - Journal (Box 1)
    - Journal Calls (Box 1)
    - Commemorative Program (Box 1)
    - 80's Alums (Box 1)
    - Gracie Mansion (Box 1)
    - Edee (Box 1)
    - Lloyd and Ben Thank Yous (Box 1)
    - X-mas Cards (Box 1)
    - Schiavone Party -, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Kelada Party, 1991 October (Box 1)
    - LA, 1993 December (Box 1)
    - Badham Party, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Talia Shire, 1993 January 17 (Box 1)
    - TV Projects Yale in TV -, 1986 (Box 1)
  - LOAN FORGIVENESS -- YALE THEATER CIRCLE -YOUNG SCHOARS PROGRAM -MISC.
    - Loan Forgiveness (Box 2)
    - Loan Forgiveness, 1992 (Box 2)
    - NH Events (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure -Data to add to Database (Box 2)
    - Lloyd Richards/Student Farewell --Invoices, 1991 May 19 (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure -Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Lloyd Richards/Student Farewell -Invitation, 1991 May 19 (Box 2)
    - Lloyd Richards/Student Farewell -Invitation List, 1991 May 19 (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure Award Lists (with C. Evans notes) (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure Public Relations initiatives (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure Bills (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure -Golden Age of TV Research (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure -Next Steps (Box 2)
    - Research Forms (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure -First drafts of orig. database and report, 1992 August (Box 2)
    - Indiv's Name Lists -Benefits Committee Mailing (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure -Federal Theater Project Research (Box 2)
    - LA Brochure -Interviews (Box 2)
    - Sarah Low's project (Box 2)
    - Yale Theater Circle
      - 1993-1994 (Box 2)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 2)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 2)
    - Ben/Misc. memos (Box 2)
    - Young Scholars Program (Box 2)
    - Young Scholars Program (Box 2)
    - Young Scholars Department Head Interviews, Spring '92 Follow up letters (Box 2)
  - INDIVIDUALS
    Restricted until January 1, 2066
    - Univ. Fellows, 1989-1991 (Box 3)
    - Dean Guido Calabresi (Box 4)
    - Dean Curtis Canfield (Box 4)
  - MISC.
    - Hamlet Event Budget Documents (Box 5)
    - Hamlet Alumni Event October, 1992 October (Box 5)
    - Jobs (Box 5)
    - Hamlet Alumni Event 10/22 (Box 5)
    - Emerson Party (Box 5)
    - Yale Kickoff LA, 1992 March 9 (Box 5)
    - LA Fall, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Boston Piano Lesson, 1988 January (Box 5)
    - Piano Lesson Events AYA (Box 5)
    - Fences -, 1988 September 22-28 (Box 5)
    - Connection Day, 1989 May (Box 5)
    - Nikos Memorial Service (Box 5)
    - Alois Nagler Roast (Box 5)
    - O'Neill's Opening Night Parties (Box 5)
    - Beinecke Ah Wilderness (Box 5)
    - Ivanov Opening at Beinecke (Box 5)
    - Ivanov (Box 5)
    - Mory's Dinners, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
    - Fences LA Opening, 1988 August (Box 5)
    - CA, 1988 October (Box 5)
    - Phantom -CA -Cancelled (Box 5)
    - Boston, 1988 January (Box 5)
    - West Bank Café response cards (Box 5)
    - Connection Day (Box 5)
    - Young Scholars Benefit
      - Invitation (Box 5)
      - Timeline (Box 5)
      - Budget (Box 5)
      - Correspondence (Box 5)
      - Taper/Doolittle Details (Box 5)
    - Los Angeles AYA Event (Box 5)
    - Young Scholars Benefit Prospectus (Box 5)
    - LA Young Scholars Benefit, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Eli Rose Party, 1994 May 12 (Box 5)
    - Yale Theatre Circle Dinner -Palio, 1986 (Box 5)
    - California, 1986 December (Box 5)
    - Boston, 1986 September (Box 5)
    - Boston Dinner No-Shows (Box 5)
    - Solicitation Boston, 1986 September 30 (Box 5)
    - Boston Dinner Invites, 1986 September 4 (Box 5)
    - Arts Convocation, 1986 August 5 (Box 5)
    - Young Scholars Party hosted by Kate Burton, Sunday, 1992 April 26 (Box 5)
    - Kate Burton Party Notes, 1992 April (Box 5)
    - Backstage at Bye Bye Birdie AIDS Benefit -Canceled, 1992 March 20 (Box 5)
    - X-mas Card -, 1992 (Box 5)
    - YDAA Christmas Party and Invitations, 1992 (Box 5)
    - X-mas party (Box 5)
    - NYC, 1991 November 15 (Box 5)
    - Micunis/Kobrin Yale Theater Circle Party, Sunday, 1991 November 17 (Box 5)
    - Rose Party, 1992 May 14 (Box 5)
    - Jujamcyn Party (Box 5)
    - Shire Party, 1992 March (Box 5)
    - Jake Party, 1992 December 6 (Box 5)
    - X-mas Party, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Wash DC, 1987 December (Box 5)
    - YTC Update, 1987 October 19 (Box 5)
    - DC Le Rivage, 1987 October (Box 5)
    - Heath Party, 1987 February (Box 5)
    - West Bank Café (Box 5)
    - Fay Vincent Dinner (Box 5)
    - DC Opening Joe Turner, 1987 October (Box 5)
    - Washington DC rated prospects (Box 5)
    - Audrey Wood Opening Day / Photos, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Audrey Wood Theatre Dedication Fall, 1984 (Box 5)
  - STAGE BLUE RESPONSE CARDS
    - Stage Blue Final Gift Detail Folder (Box 6)
    - Stage Blue Quick Reference (Financial, Co-Chair and Vice Chair Contact List, Benefit Committee Contact List) (Box 6)
    - Stage Blue materials: script, book, program, invitation, copies of the tickets, and description of the stage blue event on letterhead. (Box 6)
    - Misc. copies of Stage Blue program, response cards, save the date cards, etc (Box 7)
    - Barbara Hauptmann and Alan Eisenberg (Box 7)
    - Central Development Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Office Expenses (Box 7)
    - Presidents Letters (Box 7)
    - Copies of checks (Box 7)
    - Responses to Pres. Letter (Box 7)
    - Master List (Box 7)
    - Disney (Box 7)
    - Flowers (Box 7)
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Contracts (Box 7)
    - Communication with LA (Box 7)
    - LA Meetings (Box 7)
    - Lawyers/Entertainment (Box 7)
    - LA Alumni (Box 7)
    - LA Lists from Kidd (Box 7)
    - Invitations (Box 7)
    - Mailing Last of Lists (Box 7)
    - Mathew (Box 7)
    - Westchester (Box 7)
    - Stage Blue contributors list (Box 7)
    - List to receive letter from the President (Box 7)
    - Chelsea Piers guest list and seat numbers (Box 7)
    - Totals (Box 7)
    - Guests -Final list (Box 7)
    - People to receive chatzkas (Box 7)
  - NEA, 1991-1998
    - Training Program Final Report, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Proposal NEA Prof. Theater Companies, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Final Report NEA Prof. Theater Companies, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Site Visit NEA Prof. Theater Companies, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Award Letter NEA Prof. Theater Companies, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence NEA Prof. Theater Companies, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - International Fellows (Box 9)
    - National Medal for the Arts (Box 9)
    - Letter of Intent NEA International Fellows (Box 9)
    - Rewrite (Box 9)
    - List Tax Info. General Reports from Assoc. (Nat'l) (Box 9)
    - Working File, 1995-1996 (Box 9)
    - Site Visit old info (Box 9)
    - NEA, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
    - NEA, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
    - Grant -Geography, Part 2: Asia (Box 9)
    - NEA Planning and Stabilization Application, 1998 April 30 (Box 9)
    - NEA Application FY 99 Planning and Stab. Backup (Box 9)
    - NEA Planning/Stab Talking Points, 1998 (Box 9)
    - NEA Revizor in St. Petersburg (Box 9)
    - NEA Petersberg Final Report, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
    - NEA Consortium App, "Big Night" w/centerstage, 1997 April (Box 9)
    - NEA Galileo Mahagonny Notice of Grant and Final Report Requirements (Box 9)
    - NEA Back up File, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
    - Mahagonny NEA Yale Repertory Theater, 1996-1998 (Box 9)
    - NEA Theatre Co's Contract/Award Letter, 1996-1997 (Box 9)
    - CT Commission Application, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
    - CCA Final Report, 1998 (Box 9)
    - CCA Grant App, 1997-1999 (Box 9)
    - CT Commission Final Report, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
    - CT Commission Completed Application, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
    - CT Commission Application/Draft/Backup, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
  - CCA
    - Application, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Final Report, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Final Report, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Semi-Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Application
      - 1994-1995 (Box 11)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - CT Commission on the Arts
      - Final Report BCT Year I, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
      - Application BCT Year I, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
      - Letter of Intent BCT Year I, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
      - Semi-Annual Status Report BCT Year I, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence BCT Year I, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
      - Award Letter/Contract BCR Year I, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
      - BCR Yr. III Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - BCR Yr. III Semi-Annual Status Report, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - BCR Yr. III Application, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - BCR Yr. III Award Letter/Contract, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - BCR Yr. III Final Report, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - Letter of Intent BCR Year II, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - Award Letter/Contract BCR Year II, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence BCR Year II, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - Semi-Annual Status Report BCR Year II, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - Final Report BCR Year II, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - NEA
    - Professional Theater Training Proposal, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training Letter of Intent, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training Final Report, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Letter of Accreditation (for Theatre Training proposal) (Box 11)
    - Theater Training FINAL REPORT, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Training Contract/Award Letter, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Training Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Training Site Visit, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Training Letter of Intent, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training Letter of Intent, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training Site Visit, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training Contract/Award Letter, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Training Theater Training Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
    - Training Program Award Letter, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Training Program Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Training Program Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Training Program Revised Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Training Program Letter of Intent, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Presenters Final Report, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Presenters Contract/Award Letter, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Presenters Revised Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Presenters Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Presenters Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine Back up, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
    - Theater -Services to the field -Application, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Theater Management Final Report, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Theater Mag Application, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Services to the Field/THEATER Mag. Award Letter/Contract, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - THEATER Magazine Interim Report (Box 11)
    - Services to the Field/THEATER Mag. Application, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Services to the Field/THEATER Mag. Final Report, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Companies Contract/Award Letter, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Statement of Activities, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Narrative, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Services to the Field/THEATER Mag. Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Services to the Field/THEATER Mag. Revised Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine Revised Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Services to the Field/THEATER Mag. Final Report, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theater Presenters Progress Report, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine Contract/Award Letter, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Services to the Field/THEATER Mag. Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine Award Letter, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine Revised Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Theater Magazine Final Report, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theatre Companies Progress Reports and Final Report, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theatre Companies Contract Award Letter, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theatre Companies Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Artistic Statement (as enclosed with NEA application), 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Prof. Theater Grant, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Professional Theatre Companies
      - Final Report, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
      - Contract/Award Letter, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
      - Proposal, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
      - Letter and Reporting Requirements, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
      - Proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - Final Report, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - Progress Report, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - Revised Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
      - Contract/Award Letter, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - Site Visit, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - Progress Report, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
      - Final Report, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - STAGE BLUE
    - Submitted (Box 12)
    - New York Musicians (Box 12)
    - Vevas Communications (Box 12)
    - LA Musicians (Box 12)
    - NY Music copyists (Box 12)
    - Tams Witmark (Box 12)
    - Pentagram (Box 12)
    - Show (Box 12)
    - Edee Consulting Fee (Box 12)
    - Checks mailed out (Box 12)
    - Pier Sixty/Beverly Hilton (Box 12)
    - Copies of Vendor Checks (Box 12)
    - Expenses/Edee (Box 12)
    - Ben M. -Expenses (Box 12)
    - Distinctive Floral Designs, Inc. (Box 12)
    - Stage Blue -Income (Box 12)
    - Gala Invoices (Box 12)
    - Misc -Gala (Box 12)
    - Finlay Bros. Printing (Box 12)
    - Invalid Charges (Box 12)
    - Kidd and Co. (Box 12)
    - New Amsterdam Theatre (Box 12)
    - Sweet Concessions Jory (Box 12)
    - Dale Travis and Assoc. (Box 12)
    - Lists (Box 12)
    - USITT convention -Pittsburg (Box 12)
  - Publications and brochures
    - Yale Drama Alumni Newsletter
      - Spring 1970 (Box 13)
      - Winter 1977 (Box 13)
      - Fall 1979 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1980 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1981 (Box 13)
      - Spring 1982 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1982 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1983 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1983 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1984 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1984 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1985 (3) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1985 (Box 13)
      - Spring 1986 (Box 13)
      - Fall 1986 (Box 13)
      - Fall 1987 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1988 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1988 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1989 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1989 (Box 13)
      - Spring 1990 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1990 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1991 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1991 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1992 (2) (Box 13)
      - Fall 1992 (2) (Box 13)
      - Spring 1993 (2) (Box 13)
      - Winter 1993 (2) (Box 13)
      - Winter 1994 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 1994 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1995 (2) (Box 13)
      - Winter 1995-1996 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 1996 (2) (Box 13)
      - Winter 1996-1997 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 1997 (2) (Box 13)
      - Winter 1997-1998 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 1998 (2) (Box 13)
      - Winter 1998-1999 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 1999 (2) (Box 13)
      - Winter 1999-2000 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 2000 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 2001 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 2002 (2) (Box 13)
      - Summer 2003 (2) (Box 13)
    - Yale School of Drama/Yale Repertory Theatre Annual Report
      - 1985-1986 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1986-1987 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1987-1988 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1990-1991 (1) (Box 13)
      - 1991-1992 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1992-1993 (2) (Box 13)
    - Bulletin of Yale University School of Drama
      - 1973 Jun 15 (Box 13)
      - 1974-1975 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 13)
      - 1977-1978 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1978-1979 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1981-1982 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1982-1983 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 13)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 13)
      - 1995-1996 (2) (Box 13)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 13)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 13)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 13)
      - 1999-2000 (2) (Box 13)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 13)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 13)
    - Yale University School of Drama/Repertory Theatre Application Brochure
      - 1994-1995 (Box 13)
      - 2000-2001 (2) (Box 13)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 13)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 13)